Muhammad Ahsan

Profile

Front End Developer with +3 years of experience in Modern Web Development and UI/UX design. Skilled at HTML/CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, React, SASS/SCSS, Creative Suite (Photoshop, Illustrator, XD), Figma. Supervised 100+ Web Development projects that resulted in an increase of 75% in

Education

Punjab College

Sep 2009 - Aug 2013

Intermediate in Computer Science

Employment

UI Designer at Septem

Oct 2015 - Jan 2016

Successfully translated subject matter into concrete design for newsletters, promotional materials and sales collateral. Created design theme and graphics for marketing and sales presentations, training videos and corporate websites.

Front End Developer at Digitalpoin8 Feb 2017 - Present

Developed numerous marketing programs (logos, brochures, newsletters, infographics, presentations, and advertisements) and guaranteed that they exceeded the expectations of our clients.

Contacts

Address

Jhelum, Punjab, Pakistan

Email

ahsanzahoor2@gmail.com

Phone

+923175991007

Portfolio

muhammadahsandev.netlify.app

Skills

HTML/CSS	Expert
JavaScript	Expert
React	Expert
Photoshop	Proficient
Illustrator	Expert
Figma	Novice
SASS/SCSS	Novice
·	